neonnettles.com 2017-09-12

# Neon Nettle | Privacy Policy | NN - The No. 1 Alternative News and Entertainment Source

ZERO HOUR DIGITAL LTD would like to point out our Privacy Policy which is applicable to any personal information, given by You to ZERO HOUR DIGITAL LTD, including any user information via any of our web sites including www.neonnettles.com. This Policy is not only a legal requirement, but is also here to give you complete confidence that your privacy is our number one priority unlike other sites.

"You" shall mean you, the user of the Site. "We/Us" means ZERO HOUR DIGITAL LTD. "User" means any user of any of our websites belonging to ZERO HOUR DIGITAL LTD, including www.neonnettles.com. "User Information" means ALL personal details, which may be provided by You to Us via the Site as described above.

We process personal data in strict compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and ALL other associated legislation.

### Data Collection

When using this website, You may encounter areas such as games, competitions, forums, shopping or video services where You may be asked to enter User Information. Such User Information will only be used for the purposes stated at the collection point and/or in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

By entering Your User Information, You accept that we may retain Your User Information and that it may be held by Us or any third party company which processes it on Our behalf.

We reserve the right to perform statistical analyses of User's behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various areas of the Site and, in addition, to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of Users that have been exposed to or who have clicked on their advertising banners. We will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties.

### Disclosure

We shall be entitled to sell or otherwise make available Your User Information in order to send You information about Us and Our affiliates, associated companies and organisations, for the following purposes including, but not limited to:

  * promotional and/or marketing material about products, services and offers;
  * market research or compliance; 
  * transfers to third parties as required; 
  * and any requirements imposed by operational law

We are not responsible for any actions or policies of any third parties who request Your User information and Users should check the applicable privacy policy of such third parties.

### Cookies

You should be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the use of Cookies. "Cookies" are small text files that store basic information that a web site can use to recognise repeat site visits and as an example, re-call your name if this has been previously supplied. We may use this to observe behaviour and compile aggregate data in order to improve the Site, target the advertising and assess general effectiveness of such advertising.

Cookies do not attach to Your system and damage Your files. If You do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows You to deny or accept the Cookie feature. Note, however, that 'personalised' services may be affected if the cookie option is disabled.

### Opt-Out

You may opt out of some tracking cookies that will be able to identify you on other networks by using the following links:

  * http://www.quantcast.com/docs/display/legal/Opt-out+of+Quantcast+Delivery
  * http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

### Security

Security is very important to Us. Security procedures are in place to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of Your User information. Your User information will not be kept longer than is necessary for the purposes stated at the collection point or in this Privacy Policy.

### Updates

You may notify Us of any updates, amendments and corrections to previously collected User Information by using the E-mail address below or the Contact section on the site.

.
